A Guide to the Jeff Trollinger Papers: Records of the Sexual Minorities Commission and Other Voices Chorus, 1990-2005
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Scrapbooks 1990-2004, undated (Box 1-7)
  - Scrapbook 1, original 2000-2004, undated. (Box 3)
    - Watch for Lessons on Changing Belief by George Will, Richmond Times Dispatch, 2003 October 15. (Frame 3:169)
    - Mass. high court says gays can legally marry there The New York Times, 2003 November 19. (Frame 3:170)
    - Mass. court strikes down gay-marriage ban The Associated Press, 2003 November 19. (Frame 3:171)
    - Redefining marriage and unraveling culture by Cal Thomas, The Roanoke Times, undated. (Frame 3:172)
    - Mass. ruling poses questions around U.S. Knight Ridder, Tribune, printed in The Roanoke Times, 2003 20 November. (Frame 3:173)
    - Gay marriage vaults to front of politically charged issues Knight Ridder, Tribune, 2003 November 21. (Frame 3:174)
    - Baptist group votes to hold its support by Alberta Lindsey, Richmond Times Dispatch, 2003 November 15. (Frame 3:175)
    - Bishop urges Massachusetts' lawmakers not to redefine marriage Catholoc Virginians, 2003 November 10. (Frame 3:176)
    - Crisis and union in Anglican Communion by Alberta Lindsey, Richmond Times Dispatch, 2003 November 1. (Frame 3:177)
    - Bishop consecrated amid talk of schism The Associated Press, 2003 November 3. (Frame 3:178)
    - The Way, undated (Frame 3:179)
    - Tables turning on 'Eye' by Gail Shister, Knight Ridder Newspapers, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, undated. (Frame 3:180)
    - Robinson sees election as a calling from God The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2003 November 1. (Frame 3:181)
    - High school program divisive? by Calvin R. Trice, Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2003 November 3. (Frame 3:182)
    - On the Brits, the French, the Church, AIDS, 'Moderates,' Etc. by Ross Mackenzie, 2003 November 23. (Frame 3:183)
    - Gay couples follow a path northward by Clifford Krauss, New York Times News Service printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2003 November 25. (Frame 3:184)
    - Many in Mass. support gay marriage The Associated Press printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2003 November 24. (Frame 3:185)
    - 'We're just so regular,' 2 say New York Times News Service printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2003 December 21. (Frame 3:186)
    - Poll: Majority backs ban on gay marriage New York Times News Service printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2003 December 21. (Frame 3:187)
    - Out-of-the-closet Officers Don't Support 'Don't Ask' by Leonard Pitts, Tribune Media Services, undated. (Frame 3:188)
    - Ex-officers decry 'don't ask' New York Times News Service printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2003 December 17. (Frame 3:189)
    - Debate Conflates the Sacred and Secular by Ellen Goodman, undated. (Frame 3:190)
    - Pope urges media to be 'responsible' The Associated Press printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 January 25. (Frame 3:191)
    - Bishops mail their marriage stance The Associated Press printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 January 25. (Frame 3:192)
    - Would-Be Polygamists Challenge Ban on Grounds of Illegal Bias by Jeff Jacoby, The Boston Globe, undated. (Frame 3:193)
    - Episcopalians gather by Alan Cooperman, Los Angeles Times and Washington Post News Service, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 January 12. (Frame 3:194)
    - Chicago priests rap church for treatment of gays by Michelle Martin, Catholic News Service, printed in Catholic Virginians, 2004 January. (Frame 3:195)
    - Abp. O'Malley urges lawyers to defend sacredness of marriage by Donis Tracy, Catholic News Service, printed in Catholic Virginians, undated. (Frame 3:196)
    - Mars Remains President's Focal Point by Ellen Goodman, undated. (Frame 3:197)
    - Suburb registers same-sex couples The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 January 26. (Frame 3:198)
    - New Sodomy law would apply only to public acts by Larry O'Dell The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, undated. (Frame 3:199)
    - U.S. gay marriage ban urged by Pamela Stallsmith, Richmond Times-Dispatch, undated. (Frame 3:200)
    - Diocese rejects same-sex unions by Alberta Lindsey, Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 1. (Frame 3:201)
    - Griswold advocates diversity The Associated Press, Richmond Times-Dispatch, undated. (Frame 3:202)
    - Ohio becomes 38th state to prohibit gay marriage, undated. (Frame 3:203)
    - Judge denies certificates of birth to gay couples by Alan Cooper, Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 5. (Frame 3:204)
    - Court rules civil unions not enough The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 5. (Frame 3:205)
    - Kentucky parish loses most of its members The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, undated. (Frame 3:206)
    - Gay-rights activists gather petitions to force fall vote Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 10. (Frame 3:207)
    - Episcopalians seeking unity by Alberta Lindsey, Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 18. (Frame 3:208)
    - Respect, love rise above wrangling by Cody Lowe, The Roanoke Times 2004 February 8. (Frame 3:209)
    - Conservatives urge Bush to take stand against gay marriage The Dallas Morning News, printed in The Roanoke Times 2004 February 8. (Frame 3:210)
    - Most Americans oppose gay marriage, poll says The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 10. (Frame 3:211)
    - Ban on gay marriage fails from Associated Press Reports, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 12. (Frame 3:212)
    - Gay marriages stand for now The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 14. (Frame 3:213)
    - Bill wouldn't allow gays some loans by Pamela Stallsmith, Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 13. (Frame 3:214)
    - Mayor hails nuptials that critics call 'stunt' The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 13. (Frame 3:215)
    - Same-sex couples will ask for licenses here by Bill Lohmann, Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 13. (Frame 3:216)
    - Quote of the Week: Leander Harding, rector of St. John's Church in Stanford, Connecticut-re: Gene Robinson, openly gay Bishop of the Episcopal Church in New Hampshire, undated. (Frame 3:217)
    - Virginia House affirms ban on gay marriages by Justin Bergman, The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 13. (Frame 3:218)
    - Why the 'M' Word Matters to Me by Andrew Sullivan, Time, 2004 February 16. (Frame 3:219)
    - Local same-sex couples seek marriage licenses by Bill Lohmann, Richmond Times-Dispatch, undated. (Frame 3:220)
    - In Culture Wars, Middle Ground Has Shifted by Ellen Goodman, Richmond Times-Dispatch Op-Ed, 2004 February 15. (Frame 3:221)
    - Presbyterian minister's reinstatement ordered Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 15. (Frame 3:222)
    - The Battle over Gay Marriage by John Cloud, Time 2004 February 16. (Frame 3:223)
    - Same-sex couples bring their hearts The Associated Press, 2004 February 15. (Frame 3:224)
    - Gay marriages probably illegal, judge says The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 18. (Frame 3:225)
    - House rejects restoring 'family rule' by Pamela Stallsmith, Richmond Times-Dispatch, undated. (Frame 3:226)
    - Scores of gay couples turned away at City Hall The Associated Press, undated. (Frame 3:227)
    - First lady: Let people debate gay marriage by Deb Riechmann, The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, undated. (Frame 3:228)
    - Gay rites go on; so does legal fight The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 17. (Frame 3:229)
    - N.H. bill would disregard gay unions The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 17. (Frame 3:230)
    - Bill would rewrite law against sodomy Richmond Times-Dispatch, undated. (Frame 3:231)
    - House passes a bill on insurance for gays Richmond Times-Dispatch, undated. (Frame 3:232)
    - Richmond Times-Dispatch letters to the editor, undated. (Frame 3:233)
    - Same-sex weddings stir activists and politicians by David Crary, The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 20 (Frame 3:234)
    - San Francisco suing state to challenge ban Los Angeles and Washington Post News Service, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 20. (Frame 3"235)
    - Gay-Marriage Issue Raises Complex Questions by A. Barton Hinkle, Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 20. (Frame 3:236)
    - Bush Hopes to satisfy his base by Dana Milbank, Los Angeles and Washington Post News Service, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 24. (Frame 3:237)
    - Short-Circuiting Democracy- Again? by Charles Krauthammer, Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 27. (Frame 3:238)
    - Bush wants ban on gay marriage The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 25. (Frame 3:239)
    - Will Va. Repeal ban on benefit? by Carol Hazard, Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 March 28. (Frame 3:240)
    - N.Y. gay couples are wed from Associated Press Reports, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 28. (Frame 3:241)
    - Rosie O'Donnell weds longtime girlfriend by Lisa Leff, The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 27. (Frame 3:242)
    - Gay marriage focus of California debate The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 27. (Frame 3:243)
    - Gay couples on marriage waiting list The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 February 29. (Frame 3:244)
    - Pope urging officials to stop marrying gays The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, undated. (Frame 3:245)
    - Minister sues over Ohio domestic registry, undated. (Frame 3:246)
    - Mr. States' Rights Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 March 5. (Frame 3:247)
    - A Marriage Primer for the Stubbornly Sane by Kathleen Parker, Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 March 1. (Frame 3:248)
    - Bush's Ban Could Prove a Toxic Brew by Ellen Goodman, Redefining Marriage Indicates Moral Decline by Walter Williams, Richmond Times-Dispatch, Op-Ed, 2004 March 3. (Frame 3:249)
    - Readers Debate Homosexual Marriage Richmond Times-Dispatch Letters to the editor, 2004 March 5. (Frame 3:250)
    - New York blocks same-sex marriages The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 March 5. (Frame 3:251)
    - Gay couples start tying knot in Ore. The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 March 4. (Frame 3:252)
    - Gay bishop avoids talks outside U.S The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, undated. (Frame 3:253)
    - More gay marriages performed in New York, undated. (Frame 3:254)
    - Mass. legislators revisit gay-marriage debate by Fred Bayles, USA Today, 2004 March 11. (Frame 3:255)
    - The debate over homosexuality is one that some theologians say threatens to split congregations by Alberta Lindsey, Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 March 7. (Frame 3:256)
    - One man's spiritual awakening is a revelation that his sexuality isn't a barrier on his path to God by David Ress, Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 March 7. (Frame 3:257)
    - Cross to Bear: Gay clergy find hostility and solace as they strive to answer their calling by Alberta Lindsey, Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 March 8. (Frame 3:258)
    - True Sanctuary: At Metropolitan Community Church, all worshippers are made welcome at the table by Alberta Lindsey, Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 March 8. (Frame 3:259)
    - Town clerks are drawing a blank on gay marriage by Cathy Lynn Grossman, USA Today, undated. (Frame 3:260)
    - Minister's Path by David Ress, Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 March 8. (Frame 3:261)
    - Top court in Calif. Blocks gay marriages from Wire Reports, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 March 12. (Frame 3:262)
    - Ban on gay marriage discriminates by Brenda Berry, Winchester, Page News: Courier, letter of the week, 2004 March 11. (Frame 3:263)
    - Panel tackles social issues by Tyler Whitley, Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 March 9. (Frame 3:264)
    - 'Gays in Church,' Gay Marriage Prompt Responses Richmond Times-Dispatch letters to the editor, undated. (Frame 3:265)
    - Gays seek to overturn ruling The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 March 13. (Frame 3:266)
    - Civil Unions: from radical to routine The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 March 9. (Frame 3:267)
    - Officials Everywhere Seem to Be Suffering from San Fran Disease by John Leo, Universal Press Syndicate, undated. (Frame 3:268)
    - Comic, Where I'm Coming From " by Barbara Brandon, Universal Press Syndicate, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, undated. (Frame 3:269)
    - Massachusetts Court Opened Can of Worms Richmond Times-Dispatch letter to the editor by McDonald Wellford, Jr., Richmond, undated. (Frame 3:270)
    - Just Say 'No' to Gay Marriage by Mary Ann Glendon, The Wall Street Journal, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 March 14. (Frame 3:271)
    - Homosexuality Sparks Intense Debate Richmond Times-Dispatch letters to the editor, undated. (Frame 3:272)
    - Methodist jury acquits gay pastor The Associated Press, undated. (Frame 3:273)
    - States still might have say on gay marriage by Adam Liptak, New York Times News Service, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 March 17. (Frame 3:274)
    - Gay-marriage backers seize opportunity by John Ritter, USA Today, 2004 March 22. (Frame 3:275)
    - Irreconcilable differences by Peter Hardin, Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 March 28. (Frame 3:276)
    - Struggle Suggests a New 'Civil War' by Leonard Pitts, Tribune Media Services, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 March 15. (Frame 3:277)
    - Congregations defy Ohio Diocese over gay-bishop issue The Associated Press 2004 March 15. (Frame 3:278)
    - Christian group leader put on leave; tried to out gays Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 March 15. (Frame 3:279)
    - School restricts access to book about gay prince, undated. (Frame 3:280)
    - Gay ex-student backed at Baylor The Associated Press, undated. (Frame 3:281)
    - 2 N.Y. ministers charged for marrying gay couples from Wire Services and Times-Dispatch resources, Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 March 16. (Frame 3:282)
    - Frank question alters debate on gay marriage by Marsha Mercer, undated. (Frame 3:283)
    - Traditional family a myth, historian says by Marilyn Rauber, Media General News Service, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 March 28. (Frame 3:284)
    - Virginia lesbian couple's goal: Reach lawmakers by Peter Hardin, Times-Dispatch Washington Correspondent, Richmond Times-Dispatch, undated. (Frame 3:285)
    - Church-trial review sought The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 April 4. (Frame 3:286)
    - Gays, lesbians denied marriage licenses in Va. By Kiran Krishnamurthy, Richmond Times-Dispatch, undated. (Frame 3:287)
    - Bush vows to protect gay workers The Associated Press undated. (Frame 3:288)
    - Lesbian minister still on family leave The Associated Press undated. (Frame 3:289)
    - Mass. says it won't wed gay outsiders New York Times News Service, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 April 25. (Frame 3:290)
    - Lutherans hire gay pastors The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 April 25. (Frame 3:291)
    - Heresy-and Schism Virginia News Leader, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 April 5. (Frame 3:292)
    - Calif. family's split widening by Lisa Leff, The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 April 5. (Frame 3:293)
    - Ban on same-sex unions goes too far, Warner says by Michael Hardy, Richmond Times-Dispatch, undated. (Frame 3:294)
    - Assembly's vote bans same-sex unions in Va. By Michael Hardy, Jeff E. Schapiro, and Pamela Stallsmith, Richmond Times-Dispatch, undated. (Frame 3:295)
    - Bush's support for ban divides GOP gay group The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, undated. (Frame 3:296)
    - Gay Marriage Steals Imagery From Blacks by Shelby Steele The Wall Street Journal, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 April 18. (Frame 3:297)
    - Same-sex couples to wed Cox News Service, undated. (Frame 3:298)
    - Methodists: Homosexuality incompatible with beliefs The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 May 2. (Frame 3:299)
    - Breakaway parish formed The Associated Press, 2004 May 2. (Frame 3:300)
    - Religious rally cry inspires just a few New York Times News Service, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 May 16. (Frame 3:301)
    - Standing where church and state meet by Michael Hill, The Associated Press, printed in Virginian Pilot, 2004 May 8. (Frame 3:302)
    - Methodist delegates vote to keep church together by Rachel Zoll, The Associated Press, printed in Virginian Pilot, 2004 May 8. (Frame 3:303)
    - Gay Day thrives on failed ban The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, undated. (Frame 3:304)
    - Some couples skip wedding The Associated Press, printed in Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2004 April 27. (Frame 3:305)
    - Next up is battle for recognition by Fred Bayles, USA Today 2004 May 17. (Frame 3:306)
  - Scrapbook 2, original 1990-1994, undated (Box 4)
    - Wading into the Mainstream, undated. (Frame 4:1)
    - Progress, slow and painful Roanoke Times and World-News, 1993 July 25. (Frame 4:2)
    - Cartoon: Don't Ask, Don't Tell, Roanoke Times and World-News, 1993 July 25. (Frame 4:3)
    - Catholic chaplain backs new policy on gays in military by Jerry Filteau, Catholic News Service, undated. (Frame 4:4)
    - If Klinger could only be here by Mark E. Rush, undated. (Frame 4:5)
    - 8 senators urge release of military-gay study The Associated Press, undated. (Frame 4:6)
    - Pentagon report: Lifting gay ban OK Los Angeles Times, undated. (Frame 4:7)
    - 12 Cartoons-Doonesbury by Gary Trudeau, undated. (Frame 4:8)
    - Lesbian ruled 'unfit parent' by Margaret Edds, Roanoke Times and World-News, 1993 September 8. (Frame 4:9)
    - Gay Marine files suit seeking reinstatement The Associated Press, printed in Roanoke Times and World-News, 1993 September 8. (Frame 4:9)
    - Senate gets tougher on gays in military Boston Globe, undated. (Frame 4:10)
    - Talk show offers deluge parties in custody case The Associated Press, undated. (Frame 4:11)
    - Gay activists outraged The Associated Press, undated. (Frame 4:12)
    - Precedent was established-but a family wasn't by Ellen Goodman, The Boston Globe, printed in Roanoke Times and World-News, 1993 September 14. (Frame 4:13)
    - "Lesbian's ex-husband takes her side The Associated Press, printed in Roanoke Times and World-News, undated. (Frame 4:14)
    - Justice isn't blind to sexuality Roanoke Times and World-News, 1993 September 15. (Frame 4:15)
    - Gay couples to speak, undated. (Frame 4:16)
    - 'Married' gays tell students of stigma of homosexuality by Stephen Foster, Roanoke Times and World-News, 1993 November 18. (Frame 4:17)
    - Gay couple tells Radford audience about society's misunderstandings by Pat Hahn, undated. (Frame 4:18)
    - Tune In, Come Out Newsweek 1993 November 8. (Frame 4:19)
    - Doonesbury by Gary Trudeau, 4 cartoons, undated. (Frame 4:20)
    - Cartoon, Where I'm Coming From by Barbara Brandon, undated. (Frame 4:21)
    - Appeals court upholds order halting gay ban The Associated Press, undated (Frame 4:22)
    - Mother wants son back before gay men adopt The Associated Press, undated. (Frame 4:23)
    - Lutherans issue sex statement Roanoke, VA, undated. (Frame 4:24)
    - Lutherans 'very upset' over report by Cody Lowe, The Roanoke Times, undated. (Frame 4:25)
    - Tour Operators and Travel Agencies Find Gay Tours a Lucrative Niche by Steven Morris, Chicago Tribune, Knight Ridder-Tribune Business News accessed via America Online, 1993 October 25 (Frame 4:26)
    - Strict gay ban added to budget The Associated Press, printed in Roanoke Times and World-News, 1993 November 18. (Frame 4:27)
    - Navy told to commission gay man The Associated Press, printed in Roanoke Times and World-News, 1993 November 17. (Frame 4:28)
    - Military gay rule gets OK Houston Chronicle, undated. (Frame 4:29)
    - Understanding Gays by Jay Mathews, Washington Post, undated. (Frame 4:30)
    - Amendment removing gay rights is blocked The Associated Press, undated. (Frame 4:31)
    - Party hopeful wins supporters by Joel Turner, undated. (Frame 4:32)
    - Tot's lesbian mother appeals custody ruling The Associated Press, undated. (Frame 4:33)
    - Experts ask court to allow lesbian custody The Associated Press, undated. (Frame 4:34)
    - Wilder-Robb feud touches on gay letter The Associated Press, undated. (Frame 4:35)
    - FBI told to stop discrimination The Associated Press, undated. (Frame 4:36)
    - Gull Friends: Lesbian lovebirds off the coast of California eyewitness, 1993 October (Frame 4:37)
    - Doonesbury by Garry Trudeau, undated, 4 cartoons, The Quigmans by Buddy Hickerson, undated, [no name], 1993 December 15. (Frame 4:38)
    - Library to reveal kids' reading The Associated Press, undated. (Frame 4:39)
    - Court: Anti-gay rule unconstitutional The Associated Press, 1993 December 15. (Frame 4:40)
    - George Mason issues 'no staring' gay rule The Associated Press, undated. (Frame 4:41)
    - Pentagon details homosexual rule The Associated Press, undated. (Frame 4:42)
    - GOP opposes benefits for same-sex partners by Warren Fiske, undated. (Frame 4:43)
    - Hot Topics section of Newsweek, 1993 December 20. (Frame 4:44)
    - Mississippi Burning Newsweek, 1993 December 20. (Frame 4:45)
    - The Invisible Mainstream by Ken Baker, undated. (Frame 4:46)
    - New council making plans for spending by Brian Kelley, Roanoke Times and World-News, 1993 December 23. (Frame 4:47)
    - Panel covers wide range, undated. (Frame 4:48)
    - Playing the Part Newsweek, 1994 February 14. (Frame 4:49)
    - The Limits of Tolerance? Newsweek, 1994 February 14. (Frame 4:50)
    - Gay officer's reinstatement considered Roanoke Times and World-News, 1994 January 8. (Frame 4:51)
    - 3 cartoons- The Far Side by Gary Larson, The Wizard of ID by Bryant Parker and Johnny Hart, Non Sequitur by Wiley, undated. (Frame 4:52)
    - Homophobia Newsweek, 1994 February 14. (Frame 4:53)
    - Liberty trustees vote to stock gay paper The Associated Press, undated. (Frame 4:54)
    - HBO features Radford lesbians; wedding may follow graduation The Associated Press, undated. (Frame 4:55)
    - Same-sex marriage opposed re: Salt Lake City, Utah, undated. (Frame 4:56)
    - Extra section, Roanoke Times and World-News, by Cody Lowe, 1994 April 10. (Frame 4:57)
    - All target groups need hate-crime law by Edward L. Strickler Jr., undated. (Frame 4:58)
    - Cable Comes Out of the Closet by Harry F. Waters, undated. (Frame 4:59)
    - Library book condones illegality by Nita McNerlin, Blacksburg, undated. (Frame 4:60)
    - Doing right by workers pays off on Wall Street by John Levin, Roanoke Times and World-News, undated. (Frame 4:61)
    - Where I'm Coming From by Barbara Brandon, undated. (Frame 4:62)
    - Court stops discharge of military gays The Baltimore Sun, undated. (Frame 4:63)
    - Lesbian mom waits and hopes The Associated press, undated. (Frame 4:64)
    - Doonesbury by Garry Trudeau, 5 cartoons, undated. (Frame 4:65)
    - Blacksburg parent fights library book about gays by Brian Kelley, Roanoke Times and World-News, 1994 March 15. (Frame 4:66)
    - Library Board delays decision on book by Marla Lee, Roanoke Times and World-News, undated. (Frame 4:67)
    - 'Roommate' stays on shelf by Brian Kelley, Roanoke Times and World-News, undated. (Frame 4:68)